He shoots! He scores! That's 2-1!
I wanna score a goal like that.
Hey, look. A girl from South Braxton High.
Their uniforms are sexy as hell.
In what way? It's all black.
That's what's great about it!
You just don't get it, man.
I like uniforms.
When I'm in uniform, I don't need
to prove who I am to anyone.
You fell for it, Noel!
That's my precious Osushi!
Today's the day I'm gonna see—
...those panties!
So you were finally able
to complete your sentence,
Balgo.
Yeah. Your attention to detail is amazing.
I love that about you, too—
C'mon, seriously! That was dangerous!
That would've actually hit anyone else!
No, it wouldn't have. I threw it
with no intention of hitting you.
Don't underestimate me, Noel.
If you think you're dealing
with the same ol' Balgo, you're—
...completely wrong.
Why don't we find you a more suitable owner?
Noel Niihashi, reporting for duty.
Noel?
It's Ninny!
Ninny! Can I get your autograph?
Me, too!
Sure.
Here.
Shake my hand, Ninny!
Mine, too!
Hey, clear the way.
Come on. Move it.
You're late! A whole crowd
showed up because of you, Niiha!
Sorry. The usual gentleman
in Front London held me up.
Could it be that you were worried
and waited here for me, Ninny?
Huh?!
O-Of course not.
Ninny!
Part of being an idol is—
Me next!
Can I get a selfie with you?
...giving fanservice to my fans.
It's time.
Hey, Ninny—
Hey, wasn't I next?
Can I get a selfie?
We're taking a shortcut
'cause you were late.
Wait, Ninny!
And I keep telling you not
to call me by my first name.
Do I need to remind you
that I have seniority?
Then will you start
calling me "Noel," Ninny?
I prefer my first name.
Well, "Niiha" is cuter, so deal with it.
Not to mention, "Noel" is a guy's name.
In Japan, it's a girl's name.
Didn't you know that?
Would you stop acting Japanese?
You've never even been to Japan.
Aw, crap.
Hi-yah!
Made it.
Though we forced our way in.
It's fine. The important thing is we made it.
Uh, if I could see your tickets, please...
You should be more grateful
for your senior's kindness.
Thank you very much...
Ninny.
Stop calling me that!
Reverse London Natural Dragon Management Agency
Wing Bind Headquarters Building
Thank you for reporting for work.
WB Pipers Chief
Billy Banx Jr.
So? Where are we going today?
WB Pipers 2nd Umbrella
Ninny
Spangcole
Ninebrook Pastures. It's a lot of fun there.
The other day, you said a place that
was crawling with bugs was fun, too.
I'm pretty sure your "fun" gauge is busted!
What are you talking about?
I'm sure you would've had a blast
if you were a frog, Ninny.
Well, that hypothetical is not the reality!
Let's get going. No matter how much you
yell about it, our destination won't change.
WB Pipers 1st Umbrella
Noel
Niihashi
Oh, fine. Let's go get us
some work experience!
Have fun!
Noel...
I wanna see... your panties.
Wait! What the hell was that flashback for?!
Well, you just said
I imagined Noel disappearing!
Because you did.
"She disappeared to Reverse London"?
C'mon, dude, that's just a fairy tale.
Most people stop believing in that
before even Santa Claus.
Whatever. Let's just stop talking about it.
Now, let's start talking
about Noel's panties!
You're even more delusional now.
It's not a delusion. It's my dream!
There's no point in sugarcoating it.
It's just wishful thinking.
Wake up already.
What was that?
Bark at him, Osushi!
So cuh-yoooot!
Wait, that's not the point here.
Think about it, dude. You're failing here
'cause you keep mentioning her panties.
You mean you don't want to see panties?
That's also not the point.
I'm telling you to become
friends with her first.
I'm having a hard time because
I haven't been able to do that.
Well, I only met her for,
like, a second last time.
Let's all go see her next time.
You're after her, too, aren't you?
Huh?
You're after her, too!
N-o-e-l!
Of course I'm not! I'm trying to help out
the buddy I've known since I was a kid...
But I mean, if she happens to
have a cute friend or something,
she could introduce me, maybe.
I knew it. I figured you
had some ulterior motive.
I saved your life, remember?
If I hadn't saved you back when we were
seven, you wouldn't be here right now.
Man, that really hurt back then.
Talk about the boonies.
I think it's lovely here. It's very peaceful.
Nope, nope, nope!
I wanna hurry up and climb the ladder, join
the Sabres, and protect the city of London!
Don't you feel the same?
I'm fine with how things are now.
This suits me quite well.
Hey!
Are you the witches from Wing Bind?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm 1st Umbrella Niihashi.
This is 2nd Umbrella Spangcole.
Uh, hello? Don't introduce me
like I'm your junior!
Well, aren't you a couple
of adorable witches?
Sorry this is so sudden, but I'd like
some help with a Rank-A harvest today.
In Japan, don't you...
kill all dragons, no questions asked?
I mean, I guess this is less barbaric, but...
I wouldn't know. I was born in London.
Why don't you know?!
Act Japanese for once!
But what I'm saying is...
there's no reason we should have to go
through this... just to get some grapes...
for some damn champagne!
What else can we do?
If a civilian were to
touch a dragon directly...
Worst case, they'd get the death penalty.
When dragons make contact with humans,
they absorb all of their negative emotions,
and turn into dark dragons.
We witches exist to be a bridge
between humans and dragons.
Please stop yapping and
just hurry up and climb.
Where do you get off talking
to your senior like that?
And how the heck are you not out of breath?
That reeks!
Where the heck are these grapes
supposed to be, anyway?
Inside their nostrils.
Seriously? This is the worst.
I wanna get promoted already!
Yes, yes.
Well? Find anything?
That's so weird.
I could've sworn she went
into this telephone booth.
I'm telling you, you dreamed it.
Or rather, it was a delusion.
I'm telling the truth.
When I came to, this thing had been replaced
by a manhole or something with "WB" on it.
"WB"?
Yeah.
If it was Reverse London,
it should've been "RL."
Let's head back.
It's almost time to feed Osushi.
It suits you way more to just be
in a daze thinking about panties.
Y-You moron!
I'm still thinking about panties
even at this very moment!
Ow...
Osushi!
O-Osushi?
Your ringtone...
That's the Dragon Ball recap music!
You're totally acting Japanese!
Hello. Niihashi here.
Oh, thank goodness you answered.
I have a favor to ask.
Could you wrap up that harvest job
and do an extermination job instead?
No. I'm hanging up now.
You're joking, right? Don't hang up!
At least let me explain!
Who is it?
Chief must be half asleep.
He's asking us to do an extermination job.
Huh?!
I can hear you.
You see, the Sabres are up north
for a practice exercise.
So why does that mean we have to go?
You already know why.
It's because we're the
strongest Pipers out there.
The location is South Braxton.
Noel, you have a coin that
goes directly there, don't you?
Niiha!
We don't have time to get there with
a phonegate! Let's use the coingate!
You seem awfully happy.
Of course I am.
This is my chance.
We're gonna save London,
make everyone take notice of us,
and I'm gonna be promoted to the Sabres!
This way!
Ow!
Something's there!
Something's there, isn't it?!
There sure is!
I can't see it, but it's definitely nearby!
H-Hang in there, Osushi!
I'll protect you!
It's coming! It's coming! It's coming!
There it is! The dark dragon!
We were able to appear right
where the sensor indicated.
Of course we were.
But what the heck is this thing
doing in Front London?
It is quite strange.
How did it conceal itself until
it was able to get this large?
Noel...
Let me see... your panties!
Say what now?
Do you know what's going on?
It said your name, so, uh...
Balgo!
I know you're there, Balgo! Get out here!
Yup, you sure do.
Whoa!
N-N-Noel is...
She's flying?!
Contact with a dragon carries
a 100-year sentence. Or worse...
The death penalty!
Let me see... your panties!
Sh-She's super mad for some reason.
Oh, man! Her angry face is super cute, too!
Ah, I see. So this is the Front London
guy you keep talking about.
I will obey the rules and kill him.
Now, hang on a sec.
Let me see... your panties!
Does that lump of fur
he's carrying look familiar?
I think it's Osushi.
What's with the super-Japanese name?
It's a puppy Balgo found.
He was very fond of it.
Must be a Disguiser.
I've never heard of them.
They're dragons that use corpses as a
disguise and become what the body is.
They were everywhere
until about the 18th century,
but they cleaned up the city and
their numbers went down, I heard.
Hey! Noel!
How can you act like that
when Osushi just died?
Osushi's not dead!
He's just a bit limper, that's all!
He's not limper, he's totally flat!
That dragon chewed him open!
Dragon? Can you actually see something?
Safety first!
First, I'm gonna take those two in.
Niiha, you take care of the dark dragon!
Will Balgo get the death penalty?
We don't get to decide that!
Let me see... your panties!
It's all right now. Just follow
my directions and get to safety!
Wait, Ninny!
Ninny!
Osushi...
Damn it.
Oh, come on. And I was so close, too.
I was planning to kill you all
by ripping you apart, one by one.
Huh? Selby?
Are you serious, Balgo?
Do I still look like Selby to you?
"Look like"?
I can only hear your voice.
Hurry up and get out of here, Balgo.
It's not like I want to kill you.
I just want to eat a witch
so I can become immortal.
Sorry, but that's just a superstition.
Well, I won't know if it's a
superstition or not until I eat you!
A bit late on the support there!
I took care of the other thing,
so I'd say I was pretty fast.
So, two Disguisers, huh?
Who's the other guy?
Selby. He's Balgo's childhood friend.
When they were seven,
they were both almost hit by a train.
Apparently, Selby tried to protect
Balgo and was badly injured.
He's still alive!
That must've been when it started.
A dragon that's been in the city and
interacting with humans for that long...
Bet you've never seen one before.
Ninny!
A-Are you okay, Noel's friend?
What are you still doing here?
Stop asking someone covered in blood
stupid questions like, "Are you okay?"
and get the heck outta here!
S-Sorry. It's just, um...
I couldn't just abandon...
Well, you should have...
Balgo.
I'm gonna eat her now.
Leave her.
Once I've eaten her and become immortal,
I'm willing to let Niihashi go.
That hurts!
Whoa! Your face is scary!
You moron! What do you think you're doing?
You love Niiha, don't you?
What? You call Noel "Niiha"?
Wow, that's new and kinda exciting!
You're only feeling "excited"
'cause you're losing a lot of blood!
What the hell are you doing, Balgo?
Did you fall for this chick, too?
Sorry, but you're gonna
have to give up on her.
No!
The one I can't abandon is you,
Selby!
What are you talking about?
Selby died protecting you
when he was seven.
I just wore Selby's corpse and
acted like him this whole time.
So you traded places with him back then?
But after that, it's been you the
whole time, right? In that case...
You've been Selby way
longer than the real Selby!
I might just be dense,
but you were always kind.
I've always thought of you
as my best friend!
How am I supposed to abandon you when
you're saying you're gonna eat someone?!
Seriously?
If you can't understand what I'm saying...
then die.
N-Noel?
Balgo.
Y-Yes, ma'am?!
Just now...
You were actually slightly cool.
I accept your feelings, Balgo.
Absolute Dragon Shatter!
Huh?
No way.
Wasn't this building up to him being
spared because you were so moved?!
Was it? When?
Okay, that's a wrap.
We kill dark dragons. Those are the rules.
And our work here is done.
Good job.
What?!
What's the meaning of this?!
Well, you know how Balgo was in
contact with a dragon for ten years?
On top of that, he got bitten,
so he turned into a dragonclad.
So what?! I don't know what
a dragonclad or whatever is,
but shouldn't he be
getting the death penalty?!
Too bad.
Dragonclads are essentially dragons,
so we have to treat them as such.
And so, we're going to
be keeping Balgo here.
So good luck with that.
H-Hey, wait a minute, Billy!
Listen here...
Noel.
He's so fast! Where'd you go?
Let me see your panties.
Well, uh, you know...
Noel, let me see your panties!
I swear he just learned that on his own!
But y'know, we should be
focusing on how amazing Osushi is,
instead of the words he keeps saying!
They're really not that deep!
Okay, okay. Line up, please.
I'll make sure to give you all some.
Thanks, Wordsworth.
You're still as cute as ever!
You'll get the Nobel Prize for
Cuteness ten years in a row!
Don't lick both... my nose and mouth...
at once... I can't breathe...
Balgo.
Yes, ma'am! You called?
Could you answer this for me?
Huh? Hey, it's Ninny!
Should I really be answering this?
Hell—
Niiha!
Why the heck are you on today's
Wing Bind Head Liners and I'm not?!
I definitely did most of the work!
U-Um... I'm sorry.
I have no idea what you're talking about—
Hey! Why the heck are you
answering Niiha's phone?!
No idea...
Do you think you're super close now
just because it's her week to look after you?
Who do you think you are?!
Only I'm allowed to answer
Niiha's phone without permission!
It seems like she's mad at me
now for some reason!
That's why I had you answer my phone.
Also, no one's allowed to answer
my phone without my permission.
Ninny, Noel, you around? It's your chief.
There's an emergency, so I was
hoping you could head to the office.
No. It's Saturday.
Are you stupid?
I'm gonna hop in the shower.
Aw, too bad. This job was worth
five times the pay and points, too.